calvinseminary.edu 2014-04-14

# Privacy Statement - Calvin Theological Seminary

##### OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

Calvin Theological Seminary (“we” or “us”) recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who visit internal.calvinseminary.edu (the “Site”) and choose to take advantage of the services offered at this Site. We believe it is important for you to know how we treat the information about you that we receive during your visits to the Site. This policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, disclose, and safeguard the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you provide to us via the Site. Please note that when you link from our Site to other web sites, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. We encourage you to take the time to read this Privacy Policy and also those of any other sites you visit, whether through a link on this Site or otherwise.  
THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES ONLY TO THIS SITE, ONLINE PRACTICES, AND DATA ACQUIRED ONLINE.

###### YOUR CONSENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND REVISIONS

We may revise the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Additionally, we may in the future add new programs to the Site that are subject to new or different privacy terms. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy when you visit our Site to review the current policy in effect at that time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when posted to the Site. By using this Site, you agree to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. Last update: November 2004.

###### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE DISCLOSE IT

When you visit our Site, we may collect Personal Information you knowingly choose to disclose via manual form submission.

###### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Calvin Theological Seminary may collect Personal Information at this Site only when you provide the information to us in connection with your participation in online services such as online payments, or when you contact us via e-mail with inquiries. Personal Information includes information such as your e-mail address, first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone numbers, and other similar information that is personally identifiable to you. We may disclose Personal Information to third parties that provide services for us and to other third parties as required by law. Currently, our use and disclosure of Personal Information is limited to the following purposes:

  * understanding the use of our Site and making improvements
  * responding to requests from or providing any necessary notices to you
  * protecting the security or integrity of our Site
  * providing the services accessed by the user to our fullest ability
  * otherwise administering or managing the Site software

###### INFORMATION SECURITY

We believe that keeping Personal Information secure is one of our most significant responsibilities. We restrict access to Personal Information about you to those employees who need to know that information to assist us in our business or to provide products or services to you. We safeguard Personal Information according to established security standards and procedures, by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards for the information.

###### E-MAIL INFORMATION

If you choose to correspond with us through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses.

###### USERS UNDER AGE 13

We do not collect or maintain information at our Site from those we know are under 13 years old, and no part of our web site is designed to attract anyone under 13 years old.

###### LINKS TO WEB SITES OPERATED BY OTHERS

When you use a link to go from this Site to a web site operated by a third party, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by third party web sites linked to or from our Site, nor for the information or content contained therein.

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy, our practices, or your dealings with this Site should be directed to our Information Technology Office at 1-616-957-6111 or [sent via email inquiry](https://calvinseminary.edu/portals/faculty-and-staff/contact-us/?category=14 "Contact").
